Class of 1887 Records, 1883-1961, 1997
Smith College Archives
Class of 1887 Records
1883-1961, 1997
Smith College. Class of 1887.
RG 80 UUID:79e6c7ea-0e41-4963-9a15-3d5e3ee65683
4 boxes (2.5 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains black and white photographs, letters, writings, albums, and information from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1887.
Historical Note
The Class of 1887 was the ninth graduating class of Smith College.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Class of 1887 Records contain materials describing the history of the Class of 1887. Types of materials include black and white photographs, letters, writings, albums, and information from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1887.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1887 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Class of 1887: Class Baby 1897 (Box 1435, Folder 1)
- Class of 1887: Baccalaureate Service 1887 (Box 1435, Folder 2)
- Class of 1887: Commencement 1887 (Box 1435, Folder 3)
- Class of 1887: Commencement Music 1887 (Box 1435, Folder 4)
- Class of 1887: Commencement Speaker 1887 (Box 1435, Folder 5)
- Class of 1887: Groups 1886-87, other n.d. (Box 1435, Folder 6)
- Class of 1887: History N.d. (Box 1435, Folder 7)
- Class of 1887: Ivy Day 1887 (Box 1435, Folder 8)
- Class of 1887: Class Letters 1943-45 (Box 1435, Folder 9)
- Class of 1887: Junior Banquet 1886 (Box 1435, Folder 10)
- Class of 1887: Junior Prom 1886 (Box 1435, Folder 11)
- Class of 1887: Reunions 1912, 1932, 1937, 1942, 1947 (Box 1435, Folder 12)
- Class of 1887: Senior Dramatics 1887 (Box 1435, Folder 13)
- Class of 1887: Senior Questionnaire 1887 (Box 1435, Folder 14)
- Class of 1887: Sophomore May Breakfast for 1885 1885 (Box 1435, Folder 15)
- Class of 1887: Sophomore Reception 1883 (Box 1435, Folder 16)
- Class of 1887: Class Supper 1887 (Box 1435, Folder 17)
- Class of 1887: Bancroft, Antoinette Louise (Photographs, etc) 1883, 1885, 1887, other n.d. (Box 1436, Folder 1)
- Class of 1887: Bigelow, Jessie Elizabeth (Photographs, etc) 1886, 1938, other n.d. (Box 1436, Folder 2)
- Class of 1887: Bliss, Annie Louise 1954, other n.d. (Box 1436, Folder 3)
- Class of 1887: Bodman, Rosa Maria (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1436, Folder 4)
- Class of 1887: Bowles, Ruth Standish (Box 1436, Folder 5)
- Class of 1887: Brown, Mabel (Photographs, etc) N.d. (Box 1436, Folder 6)
- Class of 1887: Carter, Jessie (Photographs, etc) 1889, other n.d. (Box 1436, Folder 7)
- Class of 1887: Caverno, Julia Harwood (Box 1436, Folder 8)
- Class of 1887: Clark, Hannah Belle 1887-88 (Box 1436, Folder 9)
- Class of 1887: Crew, Caroline Ladd 1887, 1903, 1961 (Box 1436, Folder 10)
- Class of 1887: Day, Carrie Elizabeth (Photographs, etc) 1883-87, other n.d. (Box 1436, Folder 11)
- Class of 1887: Day, Harriet Green (Photographs, etc) 1886 (Box 1436, Folder 12)
- Class of 1887: Fay, Lillian Watkins (Photographs) 1886, other n.d. (Box 1436, Folder 13)
- Class of 1887: Foskett, Mary Page (Photographs) 1885, other n.d. (Box 1436, Folder 14)
- Class of 1887: Gale, Alice (Letters) 1885-87, 1890-91, other n.d. (Box 1436, Folder 15)
- Class of 1887: Gale, Alice (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1436, Folder 16)
- Class of 1887: Gamwell, Helen Lincoln (Photographs) 1887 (Box 1436, Folder 17)
- Class of 1887: Giles, Anne Harper (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1436, Folder 18)
- Class of 1887: Gill, Bessie Faunce (Photographs, etc) 1997, other n.d. (Box 1436, Folder 19)
- Class of 1887: Hager, Mary Earle (Photographs) 1887 (Box 1436, Folder 20)
- Class of 1887: Holmes, Helen N.d. (Box 1436, Folder 21)
- Class of 1887: Hough, Celeste Frances (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1436, Folder 22)
- Class of 1887: Hubbard, Alice J. (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1436, Folder 23)
- Class of 1887: Hubbard, Grace A. N.d. (Box 1436, Folder 24)
- Class of 1887: Hubbell, Clara Marvin N.d. (Box 1436, Folder 25)
- Class of 1887: James, Grace Fairchild 1889, other n.d. (Box 1436, Folder 26)
- Class of 1887: James, Grace Fidelia (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1436, Folder 27)
- Class of 1887: Leavens, Sarah Hall (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1436, Folder 28)
- Class of 1887: Lewis, Maria Anna (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1436, Folder 29)
- Class of 1887: Lord, Eleanor Louisa (Box 1436, Folder 30)
- Class of 1887: Luce, Maud Lilian (Photographs) 1887 (Box 1436, Folder 31)
- Class of 1887: Mason, Elizabeth Spauldiing (Box 1436, Folder 32)
- Class of 1887: Parker, Emma Harriet (Photographs) 1886-87, other n.d. (Box 1436, Folder 33)
- Class of 1887: Pinkerton, Elizabeth Downing (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1436, Folder 34)
- Class of 1887: Porter, Allie Williams (spec.) (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1436, Folder 35)
- Class of 1887: Reed, Clara Melinda N.d. (Box 1436, Folder 36)
- Class of 1887: Shaw, Adele Marie 1941, other n.d. (Box 1436, Folder 37)
- Class of 1887: Shaw, Adele Marie (Writings) 1900, 1903-13 (Box 1436, Folder 38)
- Class of 1887: Shute, Helen Winifred (Box 1436, Folder 39)
- Class of 1887: Shute, Mary Appleton (Box 1436, Folder 40)
- Class of 1887: Smith, Antoinette Julia (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1436, Folder 41)
- Class of 1887: Van Kirk, Anne Dravo (Photographs, etc) 1948, other n.d. (Box 1436, Folder 42)
- Class of 1887: Walker, Emma E. 1883, 1885-86, 1954, other n.d. (Box 1436, Folder 43)
- Class of 1887: Walton, Mary Alice (Photographs, etc) 1918, other n.d. (Box 1436, Folder 44)
- Class of 1887: Webber, Lucie N.d. (Box 1436, Folder 45)
- Class of 1887: Williams, Clara Louise 1885 (Box 1436, Folder 46)
- Class of 1887: Woodhull, Marianna 1915-16, other n.d. (Box 1436, Folder 47)
- Class of 1887: Woodruff, Martha Charlieana (Photographs, etc) 1949-50, other n.d. (Box 1436, Folder 48)
- Class of 1887: Wright, Marion Adams (Box 1436, Folder 49)
- Class of 1887: Pinkerton (Scrapbook) Various dates (Box 1437)
- Class of 1887: Woodruff, Martha Charlieana (Autograph Album, Photo Album) Various dates (Box 1438)